let's talk today
about the results of ICICI Lombard.
Its results have just come, the quarter one
result of the 2021 financial year. As
you all know, it is a very good company
in the field of insurance and general insurance. One of them is a linked
company in the field of general insurance.
That is why it receives huge FII investment. So
fundamentally it is also a very
good company. There are two types of
insurance - health insurance, personal
insurance and general insurance. General insurance includes insurance for
your shop and
crop insurance. So,
it does insurance in this way.
Now we have come to the results of the directors. The
CM has downloaded its results.
So here you can see that the
direct premium I have reduced, that is,
GDPI, by Rs. 33.0 billion, which was
Rs. 34.8 billion in the last quarter. And you can see that we have seen a
growth of 5.3 percent.
If we separate one segment in it,
like the B group insurance, if we
separate it, then its
What happens to the growth of 60.2%, it becomes negative which
was 5.3 percent if we were including the crop
in it and if the crop is removed
then its growth is 6.2%, that is, the
crop insurance, they have a
little bit of such, so there is prostate
premium or jubilee museums,
how much income is coming from them, you know, like
what happened because of 2019, there was a
decrease in the premium, there was a decrease in the people who pay the premium,
due to this their
GDPI exploded, if we talk about its
comment, it will be strong, then it has been 99.7 percent,
which had
crossed 100 percent in the quarter of the last financial year,
fennel is an accurate reminder that if
more than this is coming then what happens, there is
income coming from premium and that the
income going out increases, this company has to make
more claims, in such a situation the
company can remain profitable, but its
health, financial book remains weak,
as the shop passes, the
most  If it happens, then he has
also written that these losses have happened
due to witnesses of his Prem Kam Hair
because no one had an accident, no one
's shop caught fire, no such incident happened due to which a
claim is made and that is
why there has been no profit and he has
also said that according to the calls we received, there were
storms and cyclones,
they were removed and the jam was removed, then his comment is
1814 percent, which means that it is even
better, if we talk about the profit of Explosives Sainik
Pvt, then it has increased by
1108 percent, which this time reached
5.31 billion rupees and last time it was
4.75 billion in the first quarter of last year
and similarly if we talk about profit i.e. profit
text, then it has increased
by 8.5 percent which has been
seen increasing a lot and has reached
3.98 billion rupees right now, last time 3.10
billion rupees, if we talk about their profit share, then
that has also been very good.  It has been
176, which is higher than the previous quarter.
Till the last quarter, it was 60 per cent
for the previous year and 68 per cent
in the same quarter. So its share is also big,
profit is also big or near and has
given good results. It is a good company,
fundamentally it is a very good company. We will
see more about it, how
strong are its fundamentals. If we talk about its history chart, then
it has given
very good returns in one year and
here if we look at the maximum result of
3 years, when a company
was listed in 2017, we can see here that it was
listed on 29 October 2017 and
its price was then, at that time
you could see the whiskey price of
682 and today if we look at its price here,
it is 1259, that is, it has given a
return of at least 90 percent, so it has given
very good returns in three years, it is a very
good company. Now let's do its peer comparison.
How appealing is tractor-bike
year wise, so let's see that.  How cheap it is
available, so companies are
getting it at the lowest price in their portfolios right now, you can see here, all of them are
getting it at the maximum price of 95.61, HDFC
Life Insurance, SBI Life Insurance, yes
ICICI Prudential Life Insurance, so all these are
student life insurance, generally
what is ICICI Lombard, it is general
insurance, here the existence therapy is
around 30, so that Islamic, it is also
available at a cheap valuation right now, but
it pays well, you cannot make it cheap,
but it is also available at a big appeal, if
we talk about its sales profit etc., it is
bigger than Ruby Compound, we can see here, if we
look at the sales, first of all, a compound growth of 10 or
15 percent has been
seen, now
in 5 years, 13 percent compound growth of 20 percent has been seen in 3 years, it has
increased only because
vehicles are increasing in India, shops are also increasing, you will fall
down and the
trend of general insurance is increasing, so there is a
possibility in the future also, there is a very good possibility that
it  The profit will be seen increasing with time
and if we look at the profit, then the profit has increased by
24 percent in 10 years due to compounding
and in 3 years there is a
compound growth of 16.31 percent. Return on equity has been 16 percent in the
last year and 16.08 percent in 3 years.
If we talk about the overall shareholding pattern, then
if we look at the shareholding pattern, then
Motors had kept its shareholding
constant here, but the
promoters had reduced their shareholding here, but on the
other hand, if we look at the interest
rate and F5, both
can see their shareholding continuously
increasing from here. FIIs have increased their shareholding to
26 percent. It is a very good share
in this case, that is why people are investing in it,
people are buying from it and the
holding has increased. You can see in this, it has
reached 14 percent and click here
and the holding has reduced because
DIIs have continuously bought shares.
Fundamentally, the company appears strong to us. It is
available at a good valuation and more FIIs can increase
their holding.  They are increasing the same
problem or the girl promoters have
reduced their share holding and there is one more thing in this
that there is no planning in this right now,
now let's see from where should we buy or not,
if we should buy then how
should we buy, so let's go straight to its chart, so you
can see here that it has come on its chart, so
this is the one which was
discovered very quickly in the crisis that came in the market, so in a way you will
also be from the capital, it is a large cap
company and if you want to invest for a long time then it
is a good company
and you can see here that for the last few days it has been at another
stand, it is
hovering around 12 12:30, for the last one and a half months,
if we look at its 5 day data then
you can see that a lot of it is being seen, here
continuously today the candle is closed but the
cameras showed green candles,
as if its result was about to be announced, so
green candles were seen forming in it,
this too is not going to move much
according to me and this is a
very good stock for the long term, it is available at the right price
and if you are thinking that  If the market does a little more
then we will take it, there is
less possibility of the market falling before the selection,
if the market clash does
not cross once then it will happen, at
least it is not going to happen before the USA elections, so
you can buy this stock on television, it is a
fixed stock that I will
invest more than for the long term, very good staff
fundamentally, so error analysis
about ICICI, how has its result been,
if you liked this video then
you can like it,
definitely join the Telegram channel, thank you for watching.